A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
34483
41 cubic feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to The Library of Virginia by Jim Valva on behalf of Bennett Funeral Home on 27 August 1993.
Biographical/Historical Information
Langdon Taylor Christian, also known as Major Langdon Taylor Christian, was born on 26 May 1853, son of William Edmund (1817-1865), a farmer, and Anne Elizabeth (Taylor) Christian (1831-1863) of New Kent County, Virginia. In 1858 Christian moved with his family to Charles City County, Virginia. His elementary education consisted of four months at a private school in Richmond, Virginia, but did not progress beyond basic reading and math. During his early teens, he commenced working on a farm in Charles City County and never returned to school. At the age of eighteen, he left his parents' farm and came to Richmond where he worked for two years in a tobacco factory. In 1872 Christian entered employment with John A. Belvin, who owned the leading furniture and undertaking business in Richmond. Christian applied himself in this endeavour as a fine finisher, varnisher, and cabinet maker, and when Belvin died in 1880 Christian succeeded him and reorganized the business to bear his name.
L. T. Christian became widely known as a funeral director and he soon entered politics. He was a member of the Richmond city council for 10 years beginning in 1888. From 1900 to 1904 he served as a delegate from Richmond in the Virginia General Assembly. Christian was also a member and leader of numerous funeral directors' and fraternal organizations, including the Masonic Home of Virginia. He had a hand in the initial organization of the Virginia Game Protective Association, the National Funeral Directors' Association (1883), the Virginia Funeral Directors Association (1887), and the United States College of Embalming (1889). In 1894 Christian co-authored a bill to regulate the practice of embalming in Virginia, a bill which became law that same year and inititated the establishment of the first state examining board of embalming in the United States. Christian also served in the Virginia National Guard: he entered the Virginia Volunteers as a private in 1872 and retired 26 years later with the rank of major. On 5 October 1881, he married his first wife Isabella "Belle" Beverley Brown. With her, Christian had three children. She died in 1928, and he married second, Katherine Dubose, who died 2 October 1935. The elder Christian died on 13 November 1935 and was interred in Hollywood Cemetery.
Langdon Taylor Christian, Jr., was born on 28 August 1893, the first son and youngest child of Langdon Taylor Christian and his first wife Isabelle "Belle" Beverley Brown. Christian graduated from McGuire's University School and became a partner in his father's business by 1920. Upon his father's death in 1935, Christian assumed the presidency of the funeral home, a position he held until his retirement in June 1974. Christian like his father was affiliated with a number of fraternal and funeral director's organizations including the National Funeral Directors Association. He married Ruth Ashmore Valentine and the couple had two children. He died 23 October 1975 and was interred in Hollywood Cemetery.
Scope and Content Information
Records, 1912-1986 (bulk 1924-1986), of the clientele of the Richmond, Virginia, funeral home organized and owned by L. T. Christian (1853-1935) and later his son L. T. Christian, Jr. (1893-1975). Within each client/decedent's file are documents pertinent to their death, burial, and/or disinterment. Documents within each file may include advertisements, agreements, brochures, burial and funeral records, death certificates, clippings, correspondence, invoices, lists, military records, notes, obituaries, pamphlets, permits, receipts, and oversize rubbings and sketches of tombstones.
Sales agreements contracted between clients/decedents and the funeral home may contain information including the decedent's birthdate and/or age, birthplace, deathdate, place of death, occupation, sex, race, residence, parents' names and birthplace, next of kin and/or spouse, marital status, place and date of interment, and the official conducting the burial/memorial service. Other details on these agreements may include funeral and burial costs, casket size, physician's name, and cause of death. Obituaries and other newspaper clippings concerning their death are also included for most decedents. There are also handwritten notes containing other information concerning the funeral arrangements in the decedent's file. These notes may include drafts of obituaries, lists of funeral attendants and pallbearers, registers of funeral and memorial visitors, and burial plot locations.
Correspondence principally consists of letters, phone messages, and telegrams exchanged between the funeral home and the decedent's family members, estate administrators, and/or executors, attorneys, government officials, and other funeral homes. The correspondence concerns funeral arrangements, payments or past debt on a funeral, gratitude for services provided, and logistics of transport of the decedent. Receipts and invoices often accompany the correspondence and note charges for corpse transport, floral arrangements, embalming, obituary notices, cemetery fees, federal (National Cemeteries), state and city burial certificates and permits, interment, and other funeral home costs. Other receipts and invoices billed by other funeral businesses (i.e. cemeteries and mortuaries) are also contained herein. Also interspersed throughout this collection are medical examiner's (autopsy) reports and embalmer's reports which note and often explain cause of death. Embalmer's reports contain extensive detail concerning mortuary cosmetology and the process of preparation of the dead.
Military records and correspondence with military officials often is included in the files for decedents who were veterans of the United States Armed Services. These include soldiers who died overseas during World War II, initially were buried in foreign gravesites, and, after the war, were disinterred and reinterred in Richmond with services provided by the L. T. Christian Funeral Home. Both death and reinterment/funeral service dates for these decedents are located in the file, but they are organized chronologically according to the year they were serviced by L. T. Christian Funeral Home. Similarly, decedents who did not serve in the military but were disinterred, relocated, and reinterred by the funeral home have been filed according to the year they were disinterred.
Other items in the collection include advertisements and pamphlets provided by funeral businesses to the funeral home, casket warranty certificates, coffin plates, dog tags, oversize tombstone wax rubbings, and oversize sketches of tombstone art.
Arrangement
This collection was arranged chronologically by year service was rendered and then alphabetically by client or decedent's surname. The finding aid was created in an Access database. The database was sorted alphabetically before conversion into EAD. Decedents' names are listed alphabetically.
Related Material
See Christian Family Genealogical Notes (LVA accession 29416).
Contents List
- Abbott, Charles Frank, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Abbott, Edward Preston, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Abernathy, James Oliver, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Abrahams, Clyde L., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Acey, Archie Edward, Jr., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ackerly, Annie P., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Ackerman, Carl W., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Ackess, Mary Ann Seneca, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Acree, Frank C., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Adair, Cornelia Storrs, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Adair, Lewis Cass, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Adair, Linnie Shumate, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Adair, Nancy Wallace, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Adair, Sidney T., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Adair, Sidney Taylor, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Adams, Annie Stokes, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Adams, Elsie Harrison, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Adams, Etta Barnes, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Adams, Fannie E., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Adams, Helen DeWitt, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Adams, Hetty Brown, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Adams, Hilda Lane, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Adams, Josephine, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Adams, Kern Fay [infant], 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Adams, Mary Anne, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Adams, Mary Cunningham, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Adams, Wade Hill, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Adams, Wilfred P., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Adamson, Arthur Vincent, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Adamson, Kathleen R., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Adamson, Mattie D., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Adamson, Thomas D., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Adamson, Weatherly, Jr., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Addis, Stevens Alastair, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Addison, Ann Lyle, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Ader, Audrey Watson, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Adkins, Martha, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Agee, Alvin Hooper, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Agnew, Jane Julia, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Akers, Alice Fulton, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Akers, Lewis Elbert, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Albright, Blanche Alma, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Albright, Minnie, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Alderman, Ernest Hamlin, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Alexander, Beulah B., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Alexander, Lucille C., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Alexander, Robert Gill, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Allaband, Lula Cooksey, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Allden, Kenneth George, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Allen, Alice Guerrard, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Allen, Charles P., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Allen, Charlotte, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Allen, Daniel Pope, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Allen, Dora, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Allen, Ella Bacon, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Allen, Fannie B., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Allen, Fannie Bell, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Allen, Frances Blunt Scott, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Allen, Francis Maury, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Allen, George Howell, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Allen, Gertrude Crane, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Allen, May Woodward, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Allen, Ray Shelton, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Allen, Richard S., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Allen, Spottswood Joseph, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Allen, Susie Ratcliffe, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Allen, Temple Spottswood, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Allen, Virginia Mikell P., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Allen, Wendell Lotts, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Allison, Mamie Wall, nd (Box 3, Folder 2)
  (located in folder with Auld, John Hamilton)
- Allison, Robert Price, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Allmond, Catharine Russell, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Almond, Mr., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Alsop, Martha Tinsley, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Alvey, Marie Parker, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Alvey, Mary Starke, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Alvey, Nannie MacGruder Borum, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Ambers, Mary Eldridge, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Ambler, Anna Neal, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ambler, Edward Cary, Jr., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Ambler, Gordon B., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Ambler, Gordon B., Jr., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Ambler, John Cary, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Ambler, John Nicholas, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ambler, Nannie Lou, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Ambrose, [infant], 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ammerman, Una Osberger, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Ammons, William Rollins, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Andersen, Eleanor, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Alexander Campbell, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Alfred Scott, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Annie M., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, Arthur, Jr., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Bessie Austin, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Charles Edward, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Constance, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Anderson, Edward C., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Eleanor Armistead, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Emily Harris, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Estelle Marguerite, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Fannie Clay, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Anderson, George Little, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Anderson, Gilray M., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Hugh B., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Anderson, James Banks, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Anderson, James T., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Anderson, Jannie Butler, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, John Churchfell, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Joseph M., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Joseph R., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Anderson, Joseph Reid, Jr., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Lelia Amelia, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Lelia Bowden, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Lelia Myers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Lelia Myers, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Leslie, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Lyle Tyler, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, Mae, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Martha C., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Mattie Fowlkes, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Maude Slater, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Robert Emmett, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Robert R., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Rosalie Slaughter, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Ross, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Sally Archer, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Samuel A., 1970 (disinterred for cremation, 1971) (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Anderson, Samuel Armistead, Jr., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Anderson, St. George M., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, Viola D., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Allen C., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Allen Calhoun, Jr., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Ann Winston Butler, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Annie Pettus, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Charles Morrison, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Denis Robert Campbell, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Edgar M., Jr., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Elizabeth, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Ella Pearl H., 1979 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Andrews, Fannie Winston, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Andrews, James Watson, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Julia B., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Julia Birchett, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Andrews, Kate Bolling, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Katherine Mosby, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Robert McGuire, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Rosa Lee, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Andrews, Violet Mary (also see Alexander W. Weddell), 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Andrews, William Birchett, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Angel, Bettie Prescott, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Angel, Mary S., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Angel, Nannie, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Angel, Rebecca L., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Angel, Richard Garland, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Angle, Charles M., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Anglin, Arthur E., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Annspaugh, Robert C., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Anthony, Bernard, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anthony, Bulah K., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Anthony, Katy V., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Anthony, Thomas Gill, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Antrim, Dorothea Lee, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Antrim, Hugh, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Antrim, Joseph Linwood, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Apperson, E. Blair, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Apperson, Mary Blassanham, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Applegate, Joan Cary, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Appler, Emily Josephine, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Applewhite, Raymond William, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Applewhite, Violet Isabelle, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Archbell, Jehu Eborn, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Archer, Anne Watson, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Archer, Archabald W., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Archer, Ella, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Archer, Essie Parke, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Archer, Floyd Virginius, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Archer, Jeanette Baird Jacob, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Archer, John Stanard, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Archer, Julia Bowie, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Archer, Mary, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Archer, Virginia Riddle, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Archer, William Meade, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Archer, William S., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Archibald, Henry Drew, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Arents, Grace E., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arionus, Shirley Jane, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Armentrout, Emma J., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Armistead, John G., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Armistead, Rosalie Fontaine Jones, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Armistead, Stanly, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Elizabeth Lee, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Harry Lee, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Armstrong, James Andrew, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Lela May, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Louise Adams, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Armstrong, Robert O., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Virginia Esthridge, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Arnold, Blanche King, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Arnold, Carroll Austin, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Arnold, Josephine A. Moore, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Arnold, Robert Bacon, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Arnold, Robert W., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Arrasmith, Thomas Milton, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Arrington, Alice Brook, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Arrington, Mary A., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Arrington, Mary Dade T., 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Arvamitis, George, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Arvin, Margaret Auld, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Ashton, Alice B., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ashworth, Lee Davis, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Atkins, Emily Adelaide, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Atkins, Fannie Puryear, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Atkins, Ida Lee Montague, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Atkins, Mary Anderson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atkinson, Avonia McClung, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Atkinson, Mary Stockard, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Atkinson, Millard Filmore, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Atkinson, Susan Jones, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Atkinson, William Bruce, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Atlee, Jacob Strickler, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Atwood, Florence Chennault, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- August, Albert T., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- August, Albert T., Jr., 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- August, Augusta Bodeker, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- August, Florence Shell, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Augustine, Carrie Neal, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Auld, John Hamilton, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Aunspaugh, Mary Patterson Walters, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Austin, Edmonia S., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Austin, Theodore B., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Austin, William Lindsay, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Avery, Emmett M., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Avery, Helen, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Babcock, Gertrude Lee, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Baber, Kenneth E., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Bacon, Kate Jarvis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bagby, Alvin Fleet, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Bagby, Ann Bailey, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bagby, Ellen Matthews, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Bagby, Everette Conway, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bagby, George William, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bagby, Philip Haxall, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Bagby, Robert Coleman, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Bagley, Amanda F., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bagley, William Archer, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Annie M., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Bailey, Charles Hudnall, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bailey, Clarence Mitchell, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Cordelia E., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bailey, Edward Garland, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Edward Gee, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Bailey, Elmer H., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Frank D., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bailey, Harry M., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bailey, Lacey Medley, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Bailey, Mattie May, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bailey, Newman Marshall, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Bailey, Rebecca Emes, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Bailey, Rhea Dean Tyler, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Steve Warren, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Tollis Bartholomew, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Bailey, Tryan C., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Baily, [infant], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Baird, Jeannett Douglas, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Baird, Mary Alice, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Baird, Sallie Howerton, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Baker, Addison, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Baker, Andrew Jackson, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Baker, Annie Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Baker, Eliza M. H., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Baker, Elizabeth Allen, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Baker, Ernest Williams (2 folders), 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Baker, Ethel Howard, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Baker, Etna Gilbert, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Baker, Gordon Phillips, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Baker, Grace T., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Baker, Harry B., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Baker, Helen, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Baker, Howell Maxwell, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Baker, Irene Dunn, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Baker, Isabelle Ball, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Baker, John Hancock, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Baker, John Hopkins, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Baker, Joseph Lawson, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Baker, Lillia Gibson, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Baker, Louise Borley, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Baker, Robert M., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Baker, William Franklin, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Balch, Emily Clark, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Baldridge, Paul Earl [infant], 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Baldwin, Florence Norfleet, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Baldwin, Frank Vernon, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Baldwin, Frank Vernon, Jr., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Baldwin, Robert Maurice, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Baldwin, Thomas Jackson, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Baldwin, Walter Preston, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Baldwin, William Lee, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ball, James May, Sr., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ball, Mary Vandegrift, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Ball, Nixon, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ballard, Anna Harrell, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Ballard, Nannie Price, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ballou, William B., Jr., 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Balock, [infant] son of Charles Wilson, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Baltz, Catherine, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Bandy, Lola Wagener, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Bandy, William Gaither, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Bane, French Keister, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Bangley, Alex R., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Banks, Adelaide Sainsbury, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Banks, Edla E., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Banks, Mary L., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Banks, Richard Whittington, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Banks, William Harmon, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Baptist, Cora H., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Baptist, Frank Earnest, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Baptist, Marie L., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Baptist, Susan Alberta Harward, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barbee, Etta B., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Barbee, Waverly Witt, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Barber, Emma W. [Rison], 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barber, Irene, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barbour, Annie Garland, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Barbour, Laura D., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Barclay, Eleanor, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Daisy T., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Edmond Moore, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Ida Estil, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bargamin, Laura, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Louise Selden Johnson, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Bargamin, Marie Therese, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bargamin, Nellie M. (2 folders), 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Bargamin, Russell, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Vincent T., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Bargamin, Vincent Walter, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Barhnill, Gordon L., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Barker, Amelia Jane, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Barker, Eustace Jasper, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Barker, Garinter, Landon, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Barker, James Brannon, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)